A Guide to the Peter F. Geithner papers FA1408
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional and personal files, second run, 1951-2011; 2; 18.02 Cubic Feet About 40 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 6 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2002-2005 (Box 70, Folder 931)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 932)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2001 (Box 70, Folder 933)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 1999-2003 (Box 70, Folder 934-937)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2002-2004 (Box 71, Folder 938-939)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2002-2003 (Box 71, Folder 940)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2002-2004 (Box 71, Folder 941-942)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI) International Advisory Board (IAB) Meeting, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 943)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI), 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 944-945)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA), 2004-2005 (Box 71, Folder 946)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Annual Meeting of Trustees, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 947-948)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Annual Members' Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 71, Folder 949)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR), 2001-2002 (Box 71, Folder 950)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) By-Laws, 1990-2003 (Box 72, Folder 951)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 72, Folder 952)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 953)
  - Conference on the Future of Asia Pacific Security Studies and Exchange Activities, Bali, Indonesia, 1992-1995 (Box 72, Folder 954-957)
  - Ford Foundation Asia Programs Regional Meeting - Jakarta, Indonesia Office, 1980-1991 (Box 72, Folder 958-960)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Semi-Annual Meeting of Trustees, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 961-962)
  - The Enterprise Challenge (TEC), undated; File contains a minidisk labelled The Enterprise Challenge. (Box 73, Folder 963)
  - The Enterprise Challenge (TEC) disk (Box 73, Folder 963)
  - Dialogue on Security in Asia: Concepts, Threats, and Assurances after 9/11, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 964)
  - Asia Perspectives, Vol. 4, No. 2 - U.S.-Asia Security Relations in the Aftermath of September 11, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 965)
  - Singapore Institute of International Affairs (SIAA) Research, Focus, and Impact brochure, undated (Box 73, Folder 966)
  - Singapore trip, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 967)
  - Trilateral Commission pamphlet, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 968)
  - N.T. Wang - International Conference on Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) in China, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 969)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 970)
  - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 971)
  - Trilateral Commission Pacific Asia Group Regional Conference, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 972)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 973)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) General Meeting: Asian Cohesion Through Development Research, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 974)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) General Meeting: Asian Cohesion Through Development Research, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 975-977)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) General Meeting: Asian Cohesion Through Development Research proceedings, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 978)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) General Meeting: Asian Cohesion Through Development Research, 2004; File contains a CD labeled The 6th ADRF General Meeting, 7-8 June 2004, Bangkok, Thailand. (Box 74, Folder 979)
  - The 6th ADRF General Meeting, 7-8 June 2004, Bangkok, Thailand CD (Box 74, Folder 979)
  - Ford Foundation Asia Rural Poverty and Resources Program (RPR) meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 74, Folder 980)
  - Ford Foundation Asia Human Rights and Governance Program (HRG) meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 981-984)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees South Africa visit, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 985)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees South Africa visit, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 986)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees visit to Technikon Northern Transvaal, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 987)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees South Africa visit, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 988)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees South Africa visit, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 989)
  - Ford Foundation Board of Trustees South Africa visit, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 990)
  - Asia Society Williamsburg Conference 25th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 991-992)
  - Ford Foundation - Hong Kong trip, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 993)
  - Ford Foundation - Jakarta, Indonesia trip, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 994)
  - Ford Foundation - Hanoi, Vietnam trip, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 995)
  - Asia Society Williamsburg Conference 25th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 996)
  - Forum on Vietnam, Cambodia, and Laos Conference - Sustainable Development in Indochina: The Challenge to Make it Responsible, Participatory, People Centered, and Equitable, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 997)
  - Harvard University Fairbank Center for East Asian Research - Conference on the Domestic Sources of U.S.-China Relations, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 998)
  - Ford Foundation - Beijing, China trip, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 999-1000)
  - Max Bell Foundation - Zavikon Asian Pacific VI Conference, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 1001)
  - Ford Foundation - New Delhi, India trip, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 1002)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office establishment, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 1003)
  - Ford Foundation Bangkok, Thailand Office, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 1004)
  - China Grantmakers Meeting, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 1005)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) U.S.-China Dialogue, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1006)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) Advisory Council Meeting, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1007)
  - National Endowment for Democracy (NED) International Forum for Democratic Studies Meeting: The Prospects for Political Change in China, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1008)
  - Ford Foundation - Bangladesh trip, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1009-1010)
  - Ford Foundation Asia Program Representatives Meeting, Bangkok, Thailand, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1011)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center Conference on Philanthropy and Cultural Context: Western Philanthropy in South, East, and Southeast Asia, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1012)
  - Ford Foundation - Thailand trip, 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 1013)
  - University of California Berkeley visit, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1014)
  - East-West Center (EWC)/National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Conference - The Emergence of China into the Global Community: Implications and Responses, 1994-1995; File contains a still image (Folder 1015) of Peter F. Geithner and the other participants of the East-West Center/National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Conference, The Emergence of China into the Global Community: Implications and Responses. (Box 76, Folder 1015-1016)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Osaka Symposium on Developing Non-Governmental Underpinnings of the Emerging Asia Pacific Regional Community, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1017)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Osaka Symposium on Developing Non-Governmental Underpinnings of the Emerging Asia Pacific Regional Community, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1018)
  - Ford Foundation - London, England trip, 1993-1995 (Box 77, Folder 1019)
  - Ford Foundation India and Nepal grant programs, 1993-1995 (Box 77, Folder 1020-1022)
  - South Korea - Indigenous philanthropy, 1994-2000 (Box 77, Folder 1023-1024)
  - Advisory Board on Human Security (ABHS) Proposed Work Programme, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 1025)
  - Helsinki Process on Globalization and Democracy, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 1026)
  - Business and philanthropy in India, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 1027)
  - Miscellaneous reports, publications, and promotional material for philanthropic, research, and education institutions, 2000-2003 (Box 78, Folder 1028-1030)
  - Philanthropy and the Non-Profit Sector in South Asia, 1997-2000 (Box 78, Folder 1031-1032)
  - Ford Foundation - South Asia non-profit sector capacity building, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 1033)
  - Pakistan - Indigenous philanthropy, 1999-2001 (Box 78, Folder 1034)
  - Affinity Group on Japanese Philanthropy (AGJP), 1996 (Box 78, Folder 1035)
  - Philippines - Indigenous philanthropy, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 1036-1037)
  - Thailand - Indigenous philanthropy, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 1038)
  - Taiwan - Indigenous philanthropy, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 1039)
  - Buddhist Compassion Relief Fund Tzu-Chi Foundation brochures, undated (Box 79, Folder 1040)
  - Thailand - Indigenous philanthropy, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 1041)
  - Thailand - Indigenous philanthropy, 1996-1999 (Box 79, Folder 1042)
  - 250 Chinese NGOS, a special report from the China Development Brief, 2001 August (Box 79, Folder 1043-1044)
  - China - Indigenous philanthropy, 1996-2000 (Box 79, Folder 1045-1047)
  - China Development Research Foundation (CDRF) notes, 2002 September 12 (Box 79, Folder 1048)
  - Successful Experiment, Remarkable Achievements: Special Issue for the 10th Anniversary of the Founding of the National Natural Science Foundation of China (NSFC), 1996 (Box 79, Folder 1049)
  - China Association of Science Foundations (CASF) 1998 National Workshop on Nonprofit Organizations - Follow-Up, 1998-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1050-1052)
  - China - Indigenous philanthropy, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1053-1054)
  - China NPO Network, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 1055)
  - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (CASS) Institute of Sociology Social Policy Research Center, 1999-2000 (Box 80, Folder 1056)
  - Miscellaneous reports regarding NPOs in China, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 1057)
  - Tsinghua University Center for NGO Studies, 1998-2001 (Box 80, Folder 1058)
  - China - Indigenous philanthropy, 1995-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1059-1061)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding economic development in China, 1999 September (Box 81, Folder 1062)
  - China - Indigenous philanthropy, 1997-2000 (Box 81, Folder 1063)
  - India - Indigenous philanthropy, 1997-2001 (Box 81, Folder 1064-1067)
  - Indonesia - Indigenous philanthropy, 1995-1999 (Box 81, Folder 1068)
  - Indonesia - Indigenous philanthropy, undated (Box 81, Folder 1069)
  - India - Indigenous philanthropy, 1992-2001 (Box 81, Folder 1070-1072)
  - NGOs in Indonesia, 1996-2001 (Box 82, Folder 1073-1074)
  - Japan - Indigenous philanthropy, 1996-2000 (Box 82, Folder 1075)
  - NGOs in Vietnam, 1995-1999 (Box 82, Folder 1076)
  - Vietnam - Indigenous philanthropy, 1995-2000 (Box 82, Folder 1077-1078)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Workshop on Comparative Global Philanthropy preliminary packet, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 1079-1080)
  - Japan - Indigenous philanthropy, 1996-2002 (Box 83, Folder 1081-1084)
  - Center for Naval Analyses (CNA) Annual Conference - China, the U.S., and Japan: Implications for Future U.S. Security Strategy in East Asia, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 1085-1086)
  - Center for Naval Analyses (CNA) reports, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Folder 1087-1089)
  - Southeast Asian Studies Conference Report, 1991-1997 (Box 84, Folder 1090)
  - The Atlantic Council of the U.S./National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) - U.S. and China Relations at a Crossroads, 1993 February (Box 84, Folder 1091)
  - Life in a Man-Made Cocoon, 1993 February 20 (Box 84, Folder 1092)
  - Nguyen Kim-Xuan holiday correspondence, 1994 December (Box 84, Folder 1093)
  - Toyota Foundation 20th Anniversary Symposia, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 1094)
  - Asia Society - Taiwan Study Mission, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 1095)
  - Ditchley Park, England meeting, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1096)
  - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, 1996 April-May; File contains a still image. It is a picture of Asia Foundation Vice President Barnett Baron's daughter that was inserted into a birth announcement. (Box 84, Folder 1097)
  - Harvard University Fairbank Center for East Asian Research - Different Roots, Different Routes, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1098)
  - Council on Foundations - Conference on Corporate Citizenship in Asia Pacific, Hong Kong, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 1099-1101)
  - Asia Society Williamsburg Conference 25th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 1102)
  - Ford Foundation - New Delhi, India trip, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 1103)
  - Max Bell Foundation – Zavikon Asian Pacific V Conference, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1104)
  - American Assembly Advisory Committee on China Meeting, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1105)
  - Institute of Southeast Asia Studies (ISEAS) - Conference on the New Asia-Pacific Order and London, England trip, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1106)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Osaka Symposium on Developing Non-Governmental Underpinnings of the Emerging Asia Pacific Regional Community, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 1107-1108)
  - Conference on The Future of Asia Pacific Security Studies and Exchange Activities, Bali, Indonesia, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 1109)
  - Ford Foundation memos - England trip, 1993 October 4 (Box 85, Folder 1110)
  - Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation (IGCC) Conference - The Asia-Pacific Region: Links Between Economic and Security Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 1111)
  - Harvard University Center for International Affairs (CFIA) Conference – The Asia-Pacific Basin: Tends to the Year 2000, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 1112)
  - Conference on The Future of Asia Pacific Security Studies and Exchanges - Planning Committee Meeting, Hong Kong, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 1113)
  - Ford Foundation - China trip, 1991-1993 (Box 85, Folder 1114)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI), 2001-2006 (Box 85, Folder 1115-1116)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Latin America Conference, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 1117)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) volume - Diaspora Philanthropy and Equitable Development in China and India, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 1118-1119)
  - Asia Society - Diaspora Philanthropy and Its Impact in China and India: A Roundtable Discussion, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 1120)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Comments on Christa L. Kuljian's paper, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 1121)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding diaspora philanthropy, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 1122)
  - Social justice philanthropy, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 1123)
  - Diaspora philanthropy, 2004-2005 (Box 86, Folder 1124-1128)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Amitav Archarya and Iain Johnston project proposal, 1998-2001 (Box 86, Folder 1129)
  - Harvard University Fairbank Center for East Asian Research - Asia Center proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 86, Folder 1130)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Ford Foundation Grant, 1997-2001 (Box 86, Folder 1131)
  - Soka University of America Pacific Basin Research Center (PBRC) - The First Five Years: A Cumulative Report for 1991-1996, 1996 July 31 (Box 87, Folder 1132)
  - Hartojo Wignjowijoto, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 1133)
  - Harvard University Asia Center, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 1134)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government - China Initiative, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 1135)
  - Harvard University - Asia related programs and institutes, 1998-2005 (Box 87, Folder 1136-1138)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - New Institutionalism in Asia Seminar, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 1139)
  - Harvard University Asia Center Executive Committee, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 1140)
  - Harvard University Asia Center South Asia Dinner, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 1141)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Government, business, and NGOs in Asia project, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 1142)
  - Harvard University Campaign - Japan, undated (Box 87, Folder 1143)
  - Promoting Democracy in the 1990s: Actors and Instruments, Issues and Imperatives - A report to the Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict, 1995 December (Box 87, Folder 1144)
  - The Field of Public Policy Analysis and Management: Retrospect and Prospect by Joel L. Fleishman, 1988 February 1 (Box 87, Folder 1145)
  - Ford Foundation Mid-Decade Review, 1987 March (Box 88, Folder 1146-1152)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation International Advisory Committee Meeting, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 1153-1155)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 1156-1157)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Invitee list, 2004 December 17 (Box 89, Folder 1158)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 1159-1161)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 1162)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2004-2005 (Box 89, Folder 1163-1164)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2004-2006 (Box 89, Folder 1165-1166)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Invitee list, 2004 December 22 (Box 89, Folder 1167-1168)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Teaching Innovation in Government (TIG), 2004-2006 (Box 90, Folder 1169-1171)
  - Performance Leadership: 11 Better Practices that Can Ratchet Up Performance by Robert D. Behn, Harvard University, 2004 May (Box 90, Folder 1172)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation Faculty Advisory Committee Meeting, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 1173-1174)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation papers, 2005-2006 (Box 90, Folder 1175-1176)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation Global Network Conference - Making Democratic Government Work: Connecting Principle and Practice, 2003-2005 (Box 90, Folder 1177-1179)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Innovations in American Government Awards Program brochure, undated (Box 90, Folder 1180)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Thailand projects, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 1181)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation Global Network Conference follow-up, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1182)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2003-2005 (Box 91, Folder 1183-1184)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Teaching Innovation in Government (TIG) website, 2005-2006 (Box 91, Folder 1185)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Teaching Innovation in Government (TIG) website, undated (Box 91, Folder 1186)
    Aside from one sticky note, original folder was empty of content.
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation - Teaching Innovations in Government (TIG) Curriculum Development Project, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1187)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation promotional material, circa 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1188)
  - The Aspen Institute Business and Society Program (BSP), 2004-2005 (Box 91, Folder 1189)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1190)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government - Vietnam AIDS Public Policy Training Project, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1191)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation training and courses, 2003-2007 (Box 91, Folder 1192)
  - Personal correspondence with Gowher Rizvi, Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation Director, 2006 (Box 91, Folder 1193)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Governance and Innovation International Advisory Committee (IAC) Meeting, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 1194)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government - Executive Education Programs promotional material, circa 2005-2006 (Box 91, Folder 1195)
  - The Aspen Institute - The Chinese in the Global Community Seminar readings, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 1196-1198)
  - Ford Foundation reports and publications, 1980-1995 (Box 92, Folder 1199-1202)
  - Ford Foundation Program Officer guides, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 1203-1206)
  - Ford Foundation internal procedures and policy guides, 1992-1993 (Box 93, Folder 1207-1210)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Annual Meeting of Trustees, 2006 (Box 94, Folder 1211)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Annual Meeting of Trustees, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 1212)
  - Rockefeller Foundation consultancy appointment - Greentree Foundation and Whitney Estate, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 1213)
  - Ford Foundation - India-China Exchanges, 1992-1993 (Box 94, Folder 1214)
  - Ford Foundation - Trip reports, 1991-1996 (Box 94, Folder 1215-1216)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office, 1988-1995 (Box 94, Folder 1217)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office, 1990-1995 (Box 94, Folder 1218-1220)
  - Ford Foundation Jakarta, Bangkok, and Manila Offices, 1985-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1221-1224)
  - Ford Foundation - Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 95, Folder 1225)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government- Turmoil at Tiananmen: A Study of U.S. Press Coverage of the Beijing Spring of 1989, 1992-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1226)
  - Miscellaneous documents regarding economic and social reforms in Asia, 1995-1996 (Box 95, Folder 1227)
  - Industrial Development Services (IDS) - Rural Non-Farm Employment: Issues and Problems, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 1228-1229)
  - Sunday Times article, 1993 December 12 (Box 95, Folder 1230)
  - Bangkok, Thailand and Hanoi, Vietnam trips, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 1231)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) consultancy appointment, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 1232)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Conference - Lessons in Rebuilding Relations between Nations: The Role of Philanthropy in Postwar U.S.-Japan Relations, 1945-1975, 2000-2004 (Box 95, Folder 1233-1235)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Conference - Lessons in Rebuilding Relations between Nations: The Role of Philanthropy in Postwar U.S.-Japan Relations, 1945-1975, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1236)
  - China Center for Economic Research at Peking University (CCER) Symposium - Perspective of the Chinese Economy: Opportunities and Challenges, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1237-1239)
  - Beijing, China trip, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1240)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1241)
  - Dartmouth College Class of 1954 50th Reunion, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1242-1243)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF), 2004 (Box 96, Folder 1244)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP)-Center of RimPac Studies Shanghai Delegation Meeting on U.S.-China-Taiwan Relations, 2003-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1245)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 2002-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1246)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - The U.S. Role in Asia, 2002-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1247)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP) U.S.-China Roundtable - East Asian Security and U.S.- China Relations in the Second Bush Administration, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 1248-1249)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP) U.S.-China Roundtable - East Asian Security and U.S.- China Relations in the Second Bush Administration agenda, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 1250)